[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "How many timezones are there in the world?",
    "options": ["12", "16", "24", "10"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the time difference between Pacific time and Eastern time?",
    "options": [
      "Pacific time is 3 hours later",
      "Pacific time is two hours earlier",
      "Pacific time is 3 hours earlier",
      "Pacific time is 2 hours later"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of these countries has the highest per capita CO2 emissions?",
    "options": ["USA", "China", "India", "UK"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "what does the abbreviation EST stand for?",
    "options": [
      "East, South Time",
      "Eastern Southern Time",
      "Eastern Standard Time",
      "It doesn't stand anything"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How many timezones are there in the Finland?",
    "options": ["3", "2", "5", "1"],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The total set of carbon emissions caused by an individual.",
    "options": [
      "carbon Cycle",
      "Carbon footprint",
      "Carbon handprint",
      "Carbon summary"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the most potent greenhouse gas?",
    "options": [
      "Fluorinated gases",
      " Carbon dioxide",
      " Nitrous gas",
      "Methane"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The main human activity adds to an individual's carbon footprint.",
    "options": [
      "usage of alternatives energies.",
      "Respiration and growth",
      "Photosynthesis by plants",
      "Usage of fossils fuel for energy"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which of transportation produces less greenhouse gas than the others?",
    "options": ["Bus", "Bike", "Train", "Taxi"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which one is not the fossil fuel?",
    "options": ["coal", "Natural gas", "oil", "wood"],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "In some countries clocks do what in the spring?",
    "option": [
      "Move ahead 1 hour",
      "Move back 1 hour",
      "Stay the same",
      "Move forward 3 hours"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is one advantage of having time zones?",
    "option": [
      "To get to work on time",
      "To make clock time the same for large parts of Earth",
      "To be different than other parts of the country",
      "There are no advantages"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "To calculate the difference in time between two places you need to know:",
    "option": [
      "That there are 15 degrees in an hour",
      "The difference in the degrees of longitude between the two places",
      "What time it is at the initial location",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Where is all time measured from?",
    "option": [
      "Greenwich Mean Time",
      "0 longitude",
      "Prime Meridian",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Approximately how wide is each time zone, in degrees?",
    "option": ["5", "10", "15", "20"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What does the abbreviation UTC stand for?",
    "option": [
      "United Time Clock",
      "Underwater Time Capsule",
      "Unstoppable Time Machine",
      "Coordinated Universal Time"
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What does the abbreviation GMT stand for?",
    "option": [
      "Great Minds discuss Time",
      "Greenwich Mean Time",
      "Good Morning, Time Traveler",
      "Global Movement in Time"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  }
]
